[
    {
        "question": "That man had his kidney ............ in his brother.",
        "choices": [
            "transplants",
            "transplanted",
            "transplant",
            "transplanting"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "transplanted"
    },
    {
        "question": "I went to the mechanic to have ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "repaired my car",
            "my car repaired",
            "my car repair",
            "my car repairs"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "my car repaired"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gulliver's Travels ............ a children's novel.",
        "choices": [
            "is",
            "are",
            "has",
            "have"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "We have studied English ............ 2010.",
        "choices": [
            "at",
            "on",
            "since",
            "for"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "since"
    },
    {
        "question": "I sleep well in ............ room.",
        "choices": [
            "own",
            "an own",
            "owning",
            "my own"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "own"
    },
    {
        "question": "............ . a teacher, I have the qualities and qualifications that make my students understand well.",
        "choices": [
            "As",
            "Like",
            "Since",
            "When"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "As"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rodayna has a cousin ............ Zamzam.",
        "choices": [
            "was called",
            "called",
            "is called",
            "calling"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "called"
    },
    {
        "question": "It was two years ............ he moved into that flat.",
        "choices": [
            "as",
            "while",
            "when",
            "since"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "since"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Mr Ashraf does ............ because he has been very ill recently.",
        "choices": [
            "is",
            "are",
            "has",
            "have"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mr Nasser is my ............ friend of them all.",
        "choices": [
            "the best",
            "the better",
            "better",
            "best"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "best"
    },
    {
        "question": "............ she was busy, she refused to help me.",
        "choices": [
            "Because of",
            "On",
            "As",
            "During"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "As"
    },
    {
        "question": "Last August, I went to Alexandria for the second time ............ 2015.",
        "choices": [
            "in",
            "since",
            "for",
            "by"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "by"
    },
    {
        "question": "I did the job well ............ agreed.",
        "choices": [
            "like",
            "for",
            "since",
            "as"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "as"
    },
    {
        "question": "We have the equipment ............ for our work.",
        "choices": [
            "needed",
            "needing",
            "need",
            "needs"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "needed"
    },
    {
        "question": "I have my blood pressure ............ every week.",
        "choices": [
            "check",
            "checks",
            "checked",
            "to check"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "checked"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ahmed hasn't gone out since he ............ home last night.",
        "choices": [
            "went",
            "has gone",
            "had gone",
            "going"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "has gone"
    },
    {
        "question": "............ own car is a KIA.",
        "choices": [
            "Him",
            "His",
            "He",
            "Himself"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "His"
    },
    {
        "question": "The last match was Salah's ............ game ever.",
        "choices": [
            "great",
            "greater",
            "greatest",
            "the greatest"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "greatest"
    },
    {
        "question": "I got a plumber ............ the water pump.",
        "choices": [
            "to fix",
            "fixes",
            "fixed",
            "to fixing"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "fixed"
    },
    {
        "question": "She left an hour ago. She hasn't returned ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "then",
            "since then",
            "already",
            "just"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "since then"
    },
    {
        "question": "I arrived home ............ mum was preparing lunch.",
        "choices": [
            "before",
            "as",
            "since",
            "on"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "as"
    },
    {
        "question": "I have my son ............ after the trees in our house's garden.",
        "choices": [
            "to look",
            "look",
            "looks",
            "to looking"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "to look"
    },
    {
        "question": "As ............ , ice is lighter than water.",
        "choices": [
            "know",
            "knows",
            "knew",
            "known"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "known"
    },
    {
        "question": "............. I was very tired, I didn't finish studying unit 2.",
        "choices": [
            "When",
            "While",
            "Since",
            "Because of"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Because of"
    },
    {
        "question": "That isn't my tablet. My ............ is a SAMSUNG.",
        "choices": [
            "own",
            "it",
            "this",
            "ones"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "own"
    }
]